Guide to the Lantern Slide Collection c. 1860-1942 PR 70
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: General Lantern Slides, 1
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Banks, 1831 (Box 53, Item PR-070-0001-0176)
    Phoenix Bank on Wall Street with view of other commercial buildings and pedestrians; Near-duplicates of Bank of New York on Wall Street with trees and pedestrians; Statues on Broadway's Park Bank; Bank of New Amsterdam.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Empire State Building, 1940 (Box 53, Item PR-070-0001-0177)
    Drawing of Empire State Building towering above misc. buildings with clouds.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Flatiron Building (Box 53, Item PR-070-0001-0178)
    Flatiron building with views down 5th Ave. and Broadway showing street lamps, pedestrians, shops and corner of Madison Square Park; Flatiron building from Madison Square Park with Sidewalk Clock, pedestrians, trolleys and shops.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Insurance Buildings, 1752 (Box 53, Item PR-070-0001-0179)
    Duplicates of Royal Exchange Building on Broad Streets with weather vane and pedestrians; Equitable Life Insurance Building looking down Broadway with clock tower and other commercial buildings; Metropolitan Life Insurance Building with view of Madison S
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Markets, 1746, 1822, 1831, 1850, 1897, 1903 (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0180)
    Duplicates of Meal and Slave Market at foot of Wall Street viewed from the water with ships and buildings; Franklin Market at Old Slip with pushcarts, pedestrians and docked ships; Old Catharine Market with pedestrians, carriages, cobblestone street and c
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Merchant's Exchange, 1831, 1841 (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0181)
    Merchant's Exchange on Wall Street with pedestrians and trees; Interior of Merchant's Exchange; Merchant's Exchange with pedestrians, flag and carriages.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--New York Cotton Exchange (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0182)
    Fisheye view of New York Cotton Exchange with buildings on Beaver and William Streets from rooftop.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Publishing, 1898, 1900's, 1904-1905 (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0183)
    Façade of The New York Herald Building with signs, large awnings, park, corner of trolley car with driver; The New York Journal and Tribune Buildings surrounded by people watching war bulletins from Battle of Santiago; The New York Times Building with hot
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Publishing, interiors (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0184)
    New York World Telegram group includes scenes in newsrooms, wire room, board rooms; photos of journalists, editors, typesetters, etc.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Real Estate (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0185)
    M. Barnett Real Estate office on Park Ave. with large signs and five men standing in front.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Restaurants and Taverns, 1765, 1793, 1812, 1889 (Box 54, Item PR-070-0001-0186)
    Architectural view of the Ferry House and Tavern; Tontine Coffee-House at Wall and Water Streets-- oil painting by Francis Guy; Badenhop's Café frontal view with café window displays with Greeley House near Union Square; Bull's Head Tavern in Bowery with
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Restaurants and Taverns--Fraunce's Tavern, 1783 (Box 55, Item PR-070-0001-0187)
    Fraunces Tavern before restoration with cobblestone streets, awnings and signs; Fraunces Tavern remodeled with awnings, pedestrians (including small boy) and a horse with wagon; Fraunces Tavern at Pearl Street with flags and pedestrians; Façade of Fraunce
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Shops, 1820, 1826, 1830, 1858, 1884, 1905 (Box 55, Item PR-070-0001-0188)
    Delicatessen on Bleeker Street with signs, cobblestone street and awnings; Old Corner Store at Greenwich Street with pedestrians and other commercial buildings; James J. Mullin's Wine & Liquor Store with Horse and cart, pedestrians, signs (including billb
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Shops, Interiors, 1872, 1876 (Box 55, Item PR-070-0001-0189)
    Shoplifting scene in fabric store from "Lights and Shadows of New York Life"; Macy's Christmas Window with passerby's peering in to see doll display for the benefit of infant asylum; Families and shoppers in Bulpin's Paris Mantilla Emporium view goods for
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Singer Building, 1912 (Box 55, Item PR-070-0001-0190)
    Full view of Singer Building with carriages and pedestrians; Singer Building tower at night with ground lighting; Singer Building with neighboring skyline and smokestacks.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Washington Building (Box 55, Item PR-070-0001-0191)
    Views of Washington Building and surrounding area and buildings, including view with portion of Bowling Green, subway, entrance, signs for shipping lines, and construction.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Commercial Buildings--Whitehall Building (Box 55, Item PR-070-0001-0192)
    Whitehall Building with Battery Park and trees in Foreground.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--From the Water, 1939, 1948, 1908 (May), 1717, 1679, 1776, 1912 (Box 55, 56, Item PR-070-0001-0193)
    Views of lower Manhattan showing skyscrapers and office buildings and Brooklyn Bridge, including ferries, docks, sailboats and barges; Skylines and shorelines of New Amsterdam; Furniss Site at Riverside; Three identical Manhattan views taken from New Jers
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings, 1674, 1800, 1814, 1831, 1852, 1861, 1871, 1897, 1954 (Box 56, Item PR-070-0001-0194)
    Block House and City Gate at Wall St.; Custom House on Wall St.; Meeting House with St. Paul's in distance; Helicopter landing on Port Authority Building on Eighth Ave.; First New York Public Bath on Norfolk St.; State St. Recruicting Office with carriage
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Aquariums, 1904, 1889, 1897 (Box 56, Item PR-070-0001-0195)
    Views of the Battery Park Aquarium showing New York Bay, pedestrians, flags, trees, steamboats, sidewalks, grass, and street lighting.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Aquariums, interiors, 1897 (Box 56, Item PR-070-0001-0196)
    Views of Central Arches in Battery Park Aquarium.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Barge Office (Box 56, Item PR-070-0001-0197)
    View of Lower New York showing Barge Office including "John E. Moore" ferryboat, flags and commercial buildings.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Castle Garden, 1850, 1852, 1825-26 (Box 56, Item PR-070-0001-0198)
    Views of Castle Garden from land and surrounded by pedestrians, trees; Castle Garden as State Emigrant Bureau with signs and flags, as well as carriages; Castle Garden with Washington Baths and flags; Castle Garden viewed from Castle William with Battery
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Castle Garden, interiors, 1855 (Box 56, Item PR-070-0001-0199)
    Castle Garden State Emigrant Bureau interior showing ceilings and columned arches, as well as crowds of people.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--City Hall, 1834, 1871, 1858, 1812, 1800, 1860, 1911, 1940 (Box 57, Item PR-070-0001-0200)
    Various City Hall Buildings, including City Hall on Pearl Street with pedestrians, Wall Street Federal Hall drawings, Broadway and Chambers Streets views with City Hall Park, City Hall covered with decoration, Fenian Ealies with soldiers on horseback and
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--City Hall, interiors, 1916, 1831 (Box 57, Item PR-070-0001-0201)
    Two views of City Hall staircase with dramatic lighting, and one view of the City Hall Council Room showing conference table and chandelier.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--City Hall--Hall of Records, 1903, 1830 (Box 57, Item PR-070-0001-0202)
    Remains of Old Hall of Records and New Hall of Records during construction; Hall of Records with crowd of men on rooftop; drawing of Hall of Records surrounded by pedestrians and trees.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Courthouses, 1897 (Box 57, Item PR-070-0001-0203)
    Appellate Court House on Madison Ave. with views of street light and decorative statues; Yorkville Court House exterior view on East 57th Street with pedestrians and awnings; Criminal Courthouse building
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Custom Houses, 1830 (Box 57, Item PR-070-0001-0204)
    2 similar drawings of with American flag on top, and streets crowded with pedestrians; 2 photos of Wall Street Custom House (National City Bank) façade with Bowling Green (one photo showing large shed on Bowling Green with crowd of pedestrians and trolley
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Detention Facilities, 1942, 1776-9, 1819 (Box 57, Item PR-070-0001-0205)
    Aerial view of Manhattan House of Detention for Men (Tombs) façade with streetcars and Seward Engineering Co.; View of Tombs from Lafayette with Bridge of Sighs and car passing, as well as street lighting and road signs; View of Tombs with Bridge of Sighs
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Federal Hall, 1834-42, 1798 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0206)
    Views of Federal Hall Façade from distance showing other buildings in area, as well as pedestrians and carriages; Two similar views of Federal Hall and the Verplanck Mansion with pedestrians; View of façade of Federal Hall; View of Federal Hall National M
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Federal Hall, interiors (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0207)
    Railing from balcony of Federal Hall, Washington's inauguration; Chair from Federal Hall
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts, 1812, 1919, 1887, 1916 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0208)
    Yorkville Fort at 61st Street and East River showing docks, ships, buildings and people; Fort Mackinack with dock and houses in foreground; Forty Fort with horse and gate; Hellgate from Fort Stewart with cannons; Refuse pit near British Fort from War of I
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort Amsterdam, 1640, 1650, 1679, 1717-1747 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0209)
    3 similar views, all cropped differently, of Ft. Amsterdam Burgess view of the fort and dock from ship filled harbor; Ft. Amsterdam from Montanus (1671-1673?) view of fort, buildings and harbor full of ships; Labadist view of Ft. Amsterdam from Brooklyn
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort Amsterdam, interiors (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0210)
    Pedestal from Ft. Amsterdam; Interior view of Ft. Amsterdam with two men talking in living room area.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort Gansevoort, 1817, 1820 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0211)
    Fort Gansevoort baptism scene (duplicates); Fort Gansevoort view with carriages (duplicates); Fort Gansevoort from Hudson River with boats, docks and other buildings
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort George, 1731-1736, 1895 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0212)
    Southwest view of Fort George with the city of New York from the water showing British ships and rowboats (2 similar slides); View from Ft. George of Inwood Valley with signs for Shady Side Grove.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort Tryon (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0213)
    Garrison well with indicative sign; Laurel Hill and meadow; Sign for remainder of Breast Works; Fort viewed from Washington Ave., Riverside view of fort and tower; Fort viewed from Fort George.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Forts--Fort Washington, 1776, 1923 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0214)
    View of Ft. Washington, including Opening of Pinehurst Ave. through site of Ft. Washington and Attack on Ft. Washington; Pinehurst view contains people, houses and a dog; Jeffries Hook Rifleman's' Redoubt--showing trees and foliage.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Government House, 1795 (Box 58, Item PR-070-0001-0215)
    Three drawings of the government house with Bowling Green, pedestrians, carriages and carts, as well as other buildings on site of Old Fort.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Hospitals, 1867 (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0216)
    Northern Dispensary view of façade at Waverly Place and Christopher Street with train tracks; Views of St. Luke's Hospital showing church, carriage and cobblestone streets with street lighting; Woman's Hospital on Park Ave. with view of park and other bui
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Institutions, 1831, 1850 (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0217)
    Institution for the Blind at Ninth Ave. in distance with pedestrians an carriages in foreground; Washington Institution and City Reservoir with smokestack.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Post Office, 1845-1875 (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0218)
    Drawings of U.S. Post Office (formerly The Middle Dutch Church) at Nassau Street with pedestrians and flags.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Register's Office (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0219)
    Register's Office façade showing awnings and pedestrians; Register's Office (formerly the Provost British Prison) showing lawn and pedestrians, corner view.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Reservoir, 1831 (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0220)
    Two slides of Ivy-covered Croton Reservoir surrounded by pedestrians and showing street lamps on 5th Ave and 42nd St. (one of these is an aerial view); Two drawings of the Reservoir on 13th Street east of 4th Ave. showing pedestrians, chimneys and carriag
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Stadt Huys (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0221)
    Stadt Huys weathervane from 17th century; Stadt Huys on Pearl Street showing other buildings and ships, as well as harbor and shoreline.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Tammany Hall, 1830 (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0222)
    Tammany Hall surrounded by signs for Sohmer Piano Manufacturers and Tony Pastor's Theatre; Tammany Hall with pedestrians.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Treasury (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0223)
    Views of Treasury steps and façade with statue and pedestrians.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Government and Public Buildings--Welfare Facilities, 1735, 1821, 1881, 1902, 1850, 1794-1806 (Box 59, Item PR-070-0001-0224)
    Bloomingdale Asylum façade with driveway and front lawn; Children's Aid Society in Chelsea with pedestrians and carts; The Poor House near City Hall with elderly person in front; Leake and Watts Orphan Home on 110th St. with façade, lawn and trees; Bloomi
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Harbor, 1650, 1671, 1679, 1717-1720, 1756-1761, 1831, 1851, 1880, 1922, 1939 (Box 60, Item PR-070-0001-0225)
    Bay from Hudson River showing steamboats and docks; Upper Bay from Hudson pier showing steamboats and Statue of Liberty; Harbor with sailboats and boathouse; Steamboats and barges in New York Harbor; New York Harbor with various steamships and sailboats a
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Harbor--Battery, 1830, 1731-1736, 1889, 1869 (Box 60, Item PR-070-0001-0226)
    Bay and harbor of New York from the Battery with Castle Clinton and pedestrians; View from harbor of Battery and Castle Clinton with ships and rowboats; New York Harbor from Battery with Castle Clinton, Castle Garden and pedestrians; Battery view from wat
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Harbor--Ferry Terminals & Slips, 1904, 1820?, 1740, 1858 (Box 60, Item PR-070-0001-0227)
    Whitehall Street showing South Brooklyn Ferry Terminal, trolley buses and tracks; Astoria Ferry at 92nd Street from East River Park with industrial buildings and docks; Peck Slip Ferry and Ferry Terminal shown with carriages, barrels and commercial buildi
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Harbor--Piers and Wharves, 1679, 1680, 1839, 1879 (Box 60, Item PR-070-0001-0228)
    Wet docks at Foot of Broad Street with buildings and ships; Pier A on the Hudson (North River) showing river, distinguished gentlemen and you boy sitting on sawhorse; Sunbathers and pedestrians under Coney Island dock showing ocean, young women, children
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Harbor--Shipbuilding Industry (Box 60, Item PR-070-0001-0229)
    New York Steamer on floating dry dock in East River showing warehouses; Ship "Hamilton" carried by horse-drawn cart through crowded street past residential houses
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Harbor--Steamboats, 1948, 1928, 1938 (Box 60, Item PR-070-0001-0230)
    Duplicates of lower New York from Jersey City with steamboats in Bay and cityscape; Steamboat "Sirius" deck crowded with formally-dressed women and families; Steamboat in distance with sunset; Steamboats with Manhattan skyscrapers, harbor and skyline in b
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Hotels (Box 61, Item PR-070-0001-0231)
    Images of Hotels, including Adelphia Hotel, Astor House, Hotel Bartholdi, Breevourt House, Claremont Hotel, Corbett's Hotel (this may not be Manhattan?), the 5th Ave. Hotel, Lafayette, Hotel Netherland, Plaza Hotel, Rector's, St. Charles Hotel, Waldorf-As
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Libraries, 1831, 1908, 1906, 1840-1853 (Box 61, Item PR-070-0001-0232)
    Astor Library--diagrams of rotunda and audience hall and library from A.J. Davis collection; Clinton Hall at Beekman St. with bookstore and pedestrians; Columbia University Library stairs and statues with fountain and students; Jackson Square Branch Libra
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Libraries, interiors, 1939, 1770 (Box 61, Item PR-070-0001-0233)
    Old New-York Historical Society Library filled with paintings, books and sculptures; New New-York Historical Society Library filled with desks and containing one sculpture; Hudson Window from Library of NYHS; NYHS Library at Nassau Street with desk and bo
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues, 1919, 1910, 1914 (Box 61, 62, Item PR-070-0001-0234)
    Cleopatra's Needle in Central Park; Columbus statue in Columbus Circle at corner of Central Park; Tombstone of William Bradford; Roscoe Conklin statue in Madison Square; Peter Cooper Monument in Cooper Square; Erectheon reconstruction by A.J. Davis; Ben F
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Columbia Arch, 1893 (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0235)
    Inscription on Columbia Arch Tablet; Columbia Arch wit view down 5th Ave. showing carriages and crowds of pedestrians.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Dewey Arch (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0236)
    Frontal and side angle views of Dewey Arch with surrounding buildings and statues, as well as pedestrians and carriages.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Fort Washington Monument (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0237)
    Fort Washington Tablet and Ceremony with crowds and soldiers, as well as Fort Washington Monument with visitors.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--General Grant National Memorial (Grant's Tomb), 1897, 1910 (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0238)
    Chief of Police with Grant's Tomb in background--collage or drawing; Couples with bicycles near Grant's Tomb; Early Grant's Tomb frontal view showing sign "In His Simplicity Sublime"; Grant's Tomb with Hudson River view; Views of Grant's tomb showing ston
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Nathan Hale Statue (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0239)
    Nathan Hale Statue with view of inscription, subway station and City Hall Park with buildings in background.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0240)
    Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument on Riverside Drive in Riverside Park showing tombstones, cannon and views of pedestrians and horseback riders, as well as flag and flagpole, and surrounding nature.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Statue of Liberty (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0241)
    Views of Statue of Liberty and Bedloe's Island, including the Statue of Liberty at night and an aerial view of the island.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Tomb of St. Clair Pollock (Grave of an Amiable Child) (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0242)
    Views of Grave of an Amiable Child with Hudson River in background--urn and fence nearby Grant's Tomb
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Tombstone of Major John Smith (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0243)
    Views of reverse side of Pedestal commemorating Major John Smith with inscription--located at Fort Amsterdam.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Monuments and Statues--Washington Square Arch, 1889 (Box 62, Item PR-070-0001-0244)
    Views through Washington Arch of Judson Memorial Church with Washington Square Park; Laying of Washington Arch cornerstone ceremony; View of Fifth Ave through Washington Square Arch with pedestrians and park; View of fountain with Arch; Drawing of origina
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Museums (Box 63, Item PR-070-0001-0245)
    Barnum's American Museum at Broadway and Ann Street façade view with carriages and pedestrians on streets; Bowery Dime Museum with crowd of men standing outside looking in; The Hispanic Society of America views with neighboring buildings and Hudson River
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Museums, interiors (Box 63, Item PR-070-0001-0246)
    Interior view of Hispanic Society of America showing paintings and sculpture, as well as furniture.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Museums--New-York Historical Society, 1905-1950 (Box 63, Item PR-070-0001-0247)
    Construction scenes including views of the wing additions, views with surrounding buildings, and portraits of building committee with cornerstone; Façade reconstruction views and building completion; Dedication ceremony with portraits of Mr. Dexter and bu
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Museums--New-York Historical Society, interiors, 1905-1950 (Box 64, 65, Item PR-070-0001-0248)
    Views of corridor reconstruction in new building with workers; reconstruction of roof; Art and artifact views, including views of relics inside New-York Historical Society; Views of exhibits, including Jenny Lind; Views of Galleries, including carriage ga
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Parks and Squares, 1861, 1897 (Box 65, Item PR-070-0001-0249)
    Boy scout with flag standing next to sign for park protection; Stuyvesant Pear Tree; Chelsea Square student path; Libby Castle ("Woodcliff") in Ft. Tyron Park; Herald Square showing Corbetts and elevated train tracks, trolleys, carriages, sidewalk clock a
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Parks and Squares--Abingdon Square (Box 65, Item PR-070-0001-0250)
    Identical images of Abingdon Square with Horses and carts surrounding perimeter, showing Abingdon Hotel in foreground.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Parks and Squares--Battery Park, 1813, 1922, 1794 (Box 65, Item PR-070-0001-0251)
    Monument to Ericsson in Battery Park with Castle Clinton in background; View of Battery with New York Bay and Harbor; Flagstaff; Aerial view of Battery Park with ships, harbor and Brooklyn in distance.
  - New York-NYC-Manhattan--Parks and Squares--Bowling Green, 1906, 1942, 1860, 1895, 1830, 1875, 1831 (Box 65, Item PR-070-0001-0252)
    Bowling Green with views of the Battery, Harbor, and N.Y. Bay. De Peyster Statue at Bowling Green with surrounding buildings and pedestrians; Lawn bowling in Bowling Green; Surveys of Bowling Green; Aerial views of Bowling Green with trolley cars, carria